[
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (8 + 9 \u00d7 5) \u00f7 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "10",
      "options": [
        "12",
        "10",
        "11",
        "9"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (7 + 8 \u00d7 10) \u00f7 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "29",
      "options": [
        "30",
        "31",
        "29",
        "28"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (9 + 9 \u00d7 5) \u00f7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "54",
      "options": [
        "55",
        "53",
        "54",
        "56"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 6 \u00d7 10) \u00f7 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "16",
      "options": [
        "18",
        "16",
        "17",
        "15"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 1 \u00d7 4) \u00f7 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "3",
      "options": [
        "3",
        "2",
        "5",
        "4"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 1 \u00d7 10) \u00f7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "12",
      "options": [
        "12",
        "11",
        "13",
        "14"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (5 + 6 \u00d7 3) \u00f7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "11",
      "options": [
        "12",
        "11",
        "13",
        "10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 8 \u00d7 8) \u00f7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "37",
      "options": [
        "37",
        "36",
        "39",
        "38"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (5 + 10 \u00d7 3) \u00f7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "35",
      "options": [
        "36",
        "34",
        "37",
        "35"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (3 + 10 \u00d7 9) \u00f7 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "31",
      "options": [
        "30",
        "31",
        "32",
        "33"
      ]
    }
]